Hello everyone,
I will show you how to make a spring-loaded plate.
I have already converted the eye part of the face into a hole.
Next, click on the 3D window and find the plate.
Use the lift tool to create a spring-loaded plate.
Draw two inner lines at the front of the eye.
The length of the inner line is the same as the width of the spring-loaded plate.
It is 1.5.
After drawing, you can see its position in the 3D window.
Since the plate is in a moving state,
the inner line is symmetrical.
Next,
sew the spring-loaded plate to the inner plate.
Now, choose the spring-loaded plate in the 2D window.
Use the quick arrangement tool next to the positioning ball in the 3D window.
Arrange the plate near the eye.
To increase the simulation speed,
you can use your sending Julia to check its position.
Then, adjust the position of the center position to the three-das,
and then,
press the Allen button to change the position.
After the simulation time,
let's explore the creating a spring-loaded plate.
You can use the Edit Selection Tool to change the selection line and simulate it again.
The other side is also the same operation.
After the adjustment is complete, we will adjust the shape again.
Now the board is a C-shape.
Next, use the fixed needle tool.
Add two fixed needles to the drawstring board.
Use the Selection Tool to adjust its position.
Adjust the board to the shape of a pass-through adjustment buckle.
You can also further reduce the strength of the drawstring board.
Next, we will adjust the shape of the drawstring board.
The fixed needle can be added in the 3D window, and the same can be added in the 2D window.
Continue to adjust its shape.
After the adjustment is almost done, we enter the Connect layer in the drawstring window.
Add the adjusted buckle that has been added in advance.
Select Add to workspace with six keys.
select Open and use the glue tool to directly stick it on the drawboard,
adjust the size, and then use the positioning tool to adjust its position.
In addition, in the 3D window, you can directly adjust the size of the component,
select this component in the object window,
and in the attribute editor, you can accurately modify the size of the component.
Now let's continue to adjust the position of the component.
Insert the drawboard into the adjustment button.
After the adjustment is complete, we can start the simulation.
Since the component has already been pasted onto the drawboard,
the component is more visible.
This is done according to the simulation of the drawboard.
Now let's adjust its details.
After the adjustment is complete,
we will add a rendering thickness to the drawboard.
Now the horizontal drawstring is finished.
Now directly Ctrl D will align the finished board and copy it.
Similarly, the two boards of the hat will be frozen,
and the previously made drawstring will be frozen.
Let's simulate the parallel drawstring.
After the adjustment is complete,
we can adjust the position of the component.
we will freeze the drawstring board.
Now the parallel drawstring on both sides
is completed.
Finally, let's add the eye of the eye.
Use the twist tool to add the eye of the eye.
We need to pay attention to this.
We need to turn off the twist of the twist.
Then use the positioning tool to adjust the position of the eye of the eye.
After the adjustment is complete,
we will copy the twist to the board of the symmetrical adjustment.
Similarly, we need to adjust its position on the other side.
Finally, we will activate all the boards.
Our spring-loaded drawstring is now complete.
Let's have a look at the final results.
See you in the next video.
Good luck!